Two Films. One Love.
The Disappearance of Eleanor Rigby: Her is a drama,
romance film directed by Ned Benson.
Told from the woman's perspective, the story of a couple trying to reclaim the life and love
they once knew and pick up the pieces of a past that may be too far gone.
Eleanor Rigby, played by Jessica Chastain.
Conor, played by James McAvoy.
Professor Lillian Friedman, played by Viola Davis.
Mary Rigby, played by Isabelle Huppert.
Julian Rigby, played by William Hurt.
Katy Rigby, played by Jess Weixler.
The Disappearance of Eleanor Rigby is the collective title of three films written and directed by Ned Benson in his directorial debut, and starring Jessica
Chastain and James McAvoy, alongside a supporting cast of Viola Davis, Bill Hader, Katherine Waterston, Ciarán Hinds, Isabelle Huppert, and William Hurt.
After the film split into three parts, Him and Her  were screened at the 2013
Toronto International Film Festival as a "work in progress".
Them premiered in the Un Certain Regard section
of the 2014 Cannes Film Festival.
Them premiered in the United States on September 12, 2014, while Him and Her
were released together as double feature on October 10, 2014.
The film explores themes of new york city, loss of loved one, couple.
The tone is emotional.